I was present
that welcome to my YouTube channel, you are definitely
subscribing
that today's topic is 99
test health insurance policy, then
nowadays if you
want to take a health insurance policy then my personal
question is that if we
talk about some features of ICICI Lombard Exim policy,
you must try it once, so the
first feature is that open fa3 country
settings
that whenever you take a new policy,
you have to wait at least 1 month for this disease feeling, the
company says that if you take a policy from us
and you also get 19th positive, how to
we remove this stone for you after one month,
which can take the witnesses to a very difficult
mode, that is a very good
feature, the second teacher which has been added in these people
is food health care,
that if any Tinku witnesses
wants to get it done from his home in the sun, then
you can also keep your app of the company Lakshmi
and subscribe to that too very nicely
and the other two features are that is no  Claim bonus
that now such a body that if you have a policy or
you cannot play, then the company will
not give you a no claim bonus, after adding this the
company says that if you test positive
and you study, then we have
made it quite good, the
earlier feature that they used to do in applications, that in the
environment of development of A, the same option has been made
that even if people do not have any problem with any other disease,
delay is making it
illegal to go to the hospital, they somewhere
feel that we will never come
in contact with any witness patient, so it is
said in such a long time that you download our application
I and Take Care and we will get you
two free consultations, we will get you a doctor
who is quite qualified and
he can help you to a great extent,
friends, we have
set you two, give no physical documents,
see that till
today you had to see physical documents in any center appointment Indore,
now the company says that you should go behind our channel and see
all the documents
which takes a lot of time, this is a very
good feature  If it is such
that you do not worry whether you are a patient but you
must subscribe to it and this is my personal
opinion, hence you should have a fit length interest,
it is not necessary that you agree with this,
you should do your own study and according to your understanding,
only the positive side and
please do subscribe and like our channel,
we will keep making such videos and thank
you very much